(Recap)
What do you want to do now?
Just zone out.
Let's zone out then.
Two space cadets.
I want to spend my time with them.
Go ahead and be yourself.
I'll take it from here.
Like the fruit in Hawaii.
In full bloom.
Thank you.
for making me feel like
I'm not alone in this city.
Besides Si,
I have you too.
That line...
You do it.
Let's do it together.
We're all lucky.
Sure.
Let's give it a try this year.
Look at them.
Here's your card.
(Hands her the card)
That's already the second time
I've knocked on your door.
You're really something.
He spent two coins
on her.
Isn't that love?
From beginning to end,
have I always been
the person you were most interested in?
I've only ever
asked you out.
Okay.
♪Don't stay trapped inside your room♪
♪Outside the window,
the rain has cleared♪
♪Set reality aside♪
♪Follow your heart♪
♪What you've been longing
for is right ahead♪
♪Don't act like you didn't see it♪
♪Just be a little braver♪
♪Come closer, come closer♪
♪There's a little spark
shining in your eyes♪
♪That's the signal
of a heart coming alive♪
=Heart Signal (China Version) S9=
Here we are!
Here we are! I couldn't wait any longer.
Welcome
to WeTV's
Heart Signal (China Version) S9.
This program
is exclusively sponsored by Master Kong
Sugar-Free Jasmine Tea.
Freshly picked and scented
within 24 hours.
Every sip is as fragrant
as the first blossom.
Pantene Peach Hair Care.
Summer hair, made better.
Fresh repair, light as air.
Special thanks to Pantene
for sponsoring the show.
The innovative smart SUV, AITO M6.
Your ride to romance.
Ready to take you wherever life leads.
Build your Heart Signal.
Make every date a new surprise.
This program
is sponsored
by the LEGO Botanicals Collection.
Delicious and fun with Oreo.
Multiple flavors in every bite.
This program
is sponsored by Oreo.
No fuss, no hassle,
wake up to skin so smooth and bright.
Dewy, glowing, fresh overnight.
This program is sponsored
by Olay Glowing White Serum.
Downy In-Wash Scent Beads.
Fresh fragrance all day long.
Never lose that spark.
Thanks to Downy for sponsoring.
Xizhilang Plum Jelly.
Only you, always you.
An official sponsor
of Heart Signal Season 9.
This is the world's
sweetest
social observation reality show,
Heart Signal (China Version) S9.
(Wow)
This opening is awesome.
Let's get hyped!
I'm so happy to be here
and see everyone again.
Let's welcome
our old friend,
Ferfer (Fiona Sit)!
Fifi (Fiona Sit).
I'm so happy to be back.
While you were gone,
Dai Xu was crying his eyes out.
He was such a crybaby.
I know. I saw it.
Haitao, neither of us
can judge the other.
Seriously.
(Half a dozen of one, six of the other)
We'll count once it airs
and see who cried more.
(Crying)
(Crying from being moved)
(Crying from being touched)
(Crying from being overwhelmed)
I can't take it anymore.
Just looking at him makes me sad.
(So awkward)
(Even more awkward)
And I saw people online saying
(Cupid Zhang Chunye)
that this show
is basically
a romantic comedy.
Romantic comedy.
The comedy lane.
I'm dying.
Okay.
What were some
really memorable moments
from the last episode?
Let's talk about them.
When is Xing getting discharged?
Sun Bohan.
Sun Bohan and Wu Xingying.
Sun Bohan is smiling so brightly now.
It's like
he's been selling toothpaste.
He's always like that.
When he smiles,
his mouth is like a heart shape.
Exactly.
So cute.
He just seems
so grounded
and relaxed now.
Seeing him fall in love like this
just makes me feel good.
I want to make a meme.
Love you.
And the part where he wrote the letter
was really touching.
It felt like something
straight out of a romance movie.
I liked
Cao Yiheng and Cui Kaiyi's part
in the car.
Cui Kaiyi said the weather
looked like the end of the world,
and the two of them felt like
they were running away together.
They're the kind of couple
you can just sit back
and enjoy watching.
And "YuLiang Never Fades" scene.
One of them played the dizi,
and the other played guitar.
They were amazing.
Oh my gosh.
The vibe between them
just feels so much like home.
(Yu Yang & Liang Renfang cozy vibe)
I want to be part of it.
And there's so much chemistry
and romantic tension.
(Hit me right in the feels)
Chen Hewen and Sha Yue'er
made me feel like
my favorite couple is back.
I was honestly so relieved.
It was emotional,
then they gave us some sweetness.
It just felt like
I could finally breathe again.
Before, Chaoyue was like,
"Nope, I can't watch this."
Then, "I'm back in."
"I can do this."
"Nope, I can't watch this anymore."
"Okay, I'm back in. I'm good."
(Doing sit-ups
between shipping and not shipping them)
I think Zhao Xilun really came through.
(Cupid Du Haitao)
As long as you give him a chance.
Even if you don't,
he'll find a way to create one.
That's just
the unique charm Zhao Xilun has.
And in the end, when the three of them
ran into each other in the hallway,
they left us with another cliffhanger.
Yeah,
that ending
really got me.
I've been waiting
(Waiting impatiently)
all week.
Anxious.
It's driving you crazy.
Did he actually
give her that card?
Right?
Or is he still carrying it around
in his pocket?
I just want to know.
- Come on, everyone.
- Come on.
Let's see what happens
in this week's story.
Will Zhao Xilun successfully ask her out?
And now,
let's get into this week's
heart-fluttering story.
Here we go!
=Episode 7=
(Follow My Heart)
Where did you guys go?
We played badminton.
That's your territory.
Not really.
We're just messing around.
She's really talented.
(Complimenting)
Thanks.
This is so boring.
Let's go.
What did you guys do today?
We just walked around.
Walked around?
In Beijing?
We were just going back and forth
between the two places.
Back and forth?
Hebei and Beijing.
(Chen Hewen)
Is she going to play the piano?
She's playing the piano again.
(Starts playing piano)
Let the music speak for her.
Oh my God.
Hello.
You want? I can give it to you.
What's that?
Throat lozenges.
My throat's been bothering me.
Ah, your throat.
Do you want one?
Okay.
I'll get one for you. Come on.
He's here.
This is your photo.
Meng took it
a couple of days ago.
My photo?
Why do you have it?
Because you weren't here,
so she gave it to me first.
There's also a photo of us together.
I have something else for you.
Where is it?
I couldn't find it earlier.
Thank you.
Thanks.
You can put it on the fridge.
(Looking for the photo)
He's here.
He's here, guys.
If you don't like
how you look in this one,
I'll keep it.
(Turns away)
(Grabs)
Is that dizi yours?
Yeah.
(Observing)
He's wondering what to say.
(Sits in the corner)
He fell silent.
What's up with Sun Bohan?
So he can get massages
24 hours a day
until Xing comes back.
He wants to stay
in the best shape possible
and wait for her to come back.
Can I join you?
Here, take one.
You guys can draw together.
Sounds good.
Come on.
Pick one.
(Pick between the solo photo
and the photo of the two of them)
How about this?
You pick one.
(Let Sha Yue'er choose)
Left or right?
This one.
(Picks the photo of the two of them)
Then I'll have
your photo.
Come here for a second.
What's up?
It's just a little something.
Nothing major.
I think...
I think you should have this.
This.
(Pulls out
the stargazing room invitation card)
Stargazing room.
I feel like I should give it to you.
Yeah.
He still invited her after all.
You're the one
who opened the stargazing room?
Yeah.
But I don't know
if your schedule's pretty packed.
This is so hard.
What day did you book?
Probably tomorrow.
Okay.
What's Chen Hewen doing?
I think if I were him,
I'd probably think
Zhao Xilun is really good at this.
Zhao Xilun
is really good at seizing opportunities.
(Zhao Xilun seizes opportunities)
He never misses a chance.
Even when
it's not really an opportunity,
he still makes the most of it.
When Zhao Xilun
first got
that stargazing room card,
he hesitated for a moment.
But I knew he was definitely
going to give it to her.
(Absolutely certain)
I think Zhao Xilun is exactly
the type Sha Yue'er imagined
her ideal partner would be
from the very beginning.
But with Chen Hewen,
it's just...
She likes him.
That instant attraction.
Yeah. One is based on an idea
of someone who checks all the boxes
and has the personality she imagined,
while the other is someone
who doesn't fit
what she imagined at all,
but she just likes him.
It's that first impression.
Chen Hewen
has one really interesting quality.
He gives his competition a chance.
He lets everyone make their move.
I think
the biggest thing
is,
Sha Yue'er shouldn't mistake
Chen Hewen being polite
for him giving up.
She might think
he's just being polite again,
wondering why he isn't competing for her
or giving her enough attention.
If they could
clear up the misunderstanding,
things would be better.
Can you walk in those shoes?
Yeah.
Do you want to wear mine?
No, that's okay.
They'd slip off even more.
It's my first time getting to this spot.
Same here.
It's my first time coming down here.
(Helping her put them on)
It's a little wet, just so you know.
It's a little wet.
Here,
put my clothes underneath.
(Immediately takes off vest)
What am I supposed to do with this?
Put this on first.
Keep it from touching your skirt.
Okay, got it. I'll listen to you.
Right.
Or you might actually catch a cold.
The purpose of this vest is...
It's your second layer of waterproofing.
To give you some extra protection.
A second layer of waterproofing.
Okay.
Yeah.
You two...
She looks totally calm
while he puts the vest on her,
but deep down...
(Secretly thrilled)
They should just get together already.
See?
You don't feel as wet now, right?
Sweet.
This is seriously sweet.
(Zipping it up)
Nice.
Okay.
(A little too small)
Why is mine so tight?
It's messing up your whole outfit.
Can this be loosened a little?
This?
(Helping)
Will this make it looser?
No.
That's just how it is.
Then you can do it like this.
Let's just leave it like this.
Why is this so tight?
Does this come in different sizes?
Check and see.
Obviously not.
- That's just how it is. It's fine.
- Just buckle it up.
He's keeping such a straight face,
but he's got fireworks going off inside.
First of all, it doesn't leak.
(Trying to hold on)
Careful.
Okay.
Get on the boat.
Honestly, this is kind of scary.
Look.
(Grabs on)
Okay, I'm all settled in.
Good.
(Protecting)
All set.
Okay, let's go.
It splits into two.
Nice.
So now I can
control both sides.
What about me?
Do I need to use it?
I don't think you need to.
So I can just paddle for fun.
Yep.
Yeah.
You can basically just
hold it and play around.
Just hold it and play around.
She can't stop smiling.
(Moves it away)
I'm here to look out for Mr. Cao.
(Here to look out for Mr. Cao)
What time are you coming back tomorrow?
I probably won't be back
until a little later.
I have to go back to school tomorrow.
Then save some room for dinner.
I'll make you some soup.
Okay.
I'll be looking forward to it.
So if I want to help you,
what's the best way for me to paddle?
If you really want to help me,
just talk to me.
Keep me distracted.
Okay.
My pants are a little tight.
I'm just gonna adjust them.
You want to stand up?
Don't.
That's scary.
I'm fixing my pants.
I'm just fixing my pants.
This feels so real.
That was scary.
Like I was about to jump off the boat.
Like my confession got rejected,
so I was gonna jump off.
Well, how could you get rejected?
How could you get rejected?
They're so good at talking.
Well, how could you get rejected?
How could you get rejected?
(How could you get rejected?)
Oh, my God.
You can really feel all the love.
Indulgent love.
Yeah, indulgent love.
Yeah.
He's listening to that song again.
That's the song Xing recorded for him.
(Sun Bohan)
The one on the voice recorder.
Sun Bohan's smiling.
(Puts it away)
So you followed your heart
and made the invitation.
I wouldn't say
I followed my heart.
It was more about not wanting
to have any regrets.
I was always planning to give it to her.
If I didn't give it to her,
I wouldn't give it
to anyone else either.
Right?
Exactly.
Whatever you do,
just go with what feels right to you.
Yeah.
Since you're already here,
don't do anything you'll regret.
So I'm not setting
any expectations anymore.
I'm not going to expect her
to react a certain way,
or give me any kind of signal,
or do anything for me.
It doesn't matter anymore.
I just want to give it to her.
Give it to her and let her know
how I feel in this moment.
Right?
Yeah, you're already here.
You're already here.
That applies to relationships too.
Tomorrow.
Is it the stargazing room?
Zhao Xilun, right?
Nice.
I feel like Cui Kaiyi is seriously
living her best life at Signal House.
She's falling in love
while getting all the "tea".
You're going
to the stargazing room again.
You've already been there twice.
You will definitely get a spot tomorrow.
Will there be stars tomorrow
or the day after?
It's going to rain
the day after tomorrow.
Unbelievable.
No.
What's wrong with Sha Yue'er?
Sha Yue'er has way too much
on her mind right now.
What should I do?
How did you feel
about spending time with him today?
It was pretty good.
Pretty good again?
Didn't you two
have a rough time that day?
You said back then...
Now I'm half convinced, half doubtful
about him.
From beginning to end,
have I always been
the person you were most interested in?
I want to get to know you the most.
You want me to completely trust him?
I don't think I can do that.
Half believe him.
(Opening the stargazing invitation card)
I'm so upset.
Why are you upset?
Why, sweetheart?
I don't think "upset"
is the right way to put it.
It's more like "this is so hard".
Right now.
You need to make a choice.
Because they're both
being so brave right now.
I think you should just go
with whoever you like.
Your feelings come first.
Really?
That's how I see it.
But if things
don't work out in real life,
those feelings can fade pretty quickly.
But if you ask me, if I don't like him,
there's no way I could be with him.
It just wouldn't work.
That's true.
Yeah.
Sha Yue'er's feelings
are as messy
as her hair.
It's a mess.
Chen Hewen is looking at photos alone.
I'm so tired.
I want to do
something different tomorrow.
Are you going to write her a letter?
I want to do something meaningful.
Exactly.
Like Cui Kaiyi said,
feelings
come first.
Exactly.
If things don't work out in real life,
those feelings can fade pretty quickly.
That actually reflects
how she's feeling
right now.
Sha Yue'er is starting to hesitate too.
She's hesitating too.
I can understand
why she only half believes him.
I think what she really wants
in a relationship
is someone who will choose her
above everyone else,
and make her the only person
they truly favor.
I feel like Sha Yue'er
is at a point
where she's being
pretty honest with herself
about how she feels.
She doesn't need
to rush
into making a decision
or forcing herself to do anything.
So I actually think
she really values herself
and this relationship.
That's why
she has so much on her mind right now.
This is something
she needs to work through.
All of her inner needs
are being projected onto two people.
Zhao Xilun
and Chen Hewen.
So, Dai Xu, which one would you choose?
I'd probably lean toward Zhao Xilun.
(Cupid Dai Xu)
I think a girl
should definitely find a guy
who treats her well.
Then I'd choose Chen Hewen.
Because I think
that instant attraction
is really important.
I feel like in this world,
it's rare to really like someone.
I just want to be with someone I like.
I don't need anything else.
I can take care of myself.
(Yu Yang returns to Signal House)
Yu Yang is back.
He's looking even better now.
Once you meet someone you like,
(Looking around)
you start caring more about your looks.
Yeah.
Hello.
You're back.
I was the first one back.
I didn't see anyone.
Why hasn't she (Liang Renfang)
come back yet?
(Pinching)
(Checking the time)
They're waiting for their girls.
(Cao Yiheng)
I'm getting pretty sleepy.
I came back before sunset.
So you've been here for hours.
You're the only one here?
Zhao Xilun
went to the stargazing room.
He was the second one back.
He went to the stargazing room.
Let's wait a little longer.
Come on, Yu Yang.
Let's go downstairs and walk around.
Let's go.
They can't sit still anymore.
It's so quiet today.
Yeah.
Nobody's back.
He starts
rock climbing.
Time flies when you're doing something.
(Suddenly appears)
So cute.
Careful.
Be careful.
It feels so good
when you jump down.
(Fixing his hair)
Why aren't they back yet?
I don't know.
I really like my hair like this.
But I really want to jump down
and just fly over there.
That feels so good.
He doesn't know what to do anymore.
He's not used to
being on his own.
(Having a hard time being alone)
He's not used to being alone.
He's not used to
being on his own.
(Pretending to shoot a basketball)
What time is it already?
Why aren't they back yet?
They're not coming back.
They all went on dates.
Let's play badminton.
Sure.
(Looking)
Who's back?
Who?
Chen Hewen.
(Chen Hewen returns to Signal House)
Hello.
I got back a little late.
I got back pretty late.
Not many people are back.
It's just the three of us.
Just the three of us?
Zhao Xilun went to the stargazing room.
Zhao Xilun is at that, uh...
Oh my God.
He just found out?
He only just found out.
I'm gonna go put my stuff away first.
Go ahead.
(Jogs)
Feels like we haven't met in ages.
It's only been a day,
Chris.
Please pick a seat.
(Private Romantic Dinner, Summer Breeze)
I'll sit here.
Please.
Okay.
(Pulls out the chair)
He's really thoughtful.
Thank you.
Chris.
You're welcome.
I'm sitting down.
Go ahead.
Here.
(Hands over the food)
Thank you.
What do we have?
I'll just grab whatever.
(Sha Yue'er)
I think this is wagyu and pineapple.
This should be yakitori.
And this one's okra.
Let's dig in.
You too.
Okay.
Go ahead.
He's looking good.
I think it's what he's wearing today.
It looks good on him.
He looks pretty classy.
How do I put it?
He has that youthful vibe.
Help yourself.
Looks pretty good.
So good.
It's actually really good.
Were you busy today?
Probably about as busy as you were.
So you were pretty busy,
but you still made time to...
(Hands it over)
Thanks. Yeah.
(Zhao Xilun)
Made time to come early.
Yeah.
That means a lot to me.
How about you?
Let me tell you some good news.
What good news?
Last night,
I got an interview at Imperial College.
An interview at Imperial College?
Yeah.
That's impressive.
When's the interview?
Tomorrow.
I was on the fence about it.
I'll see if I can make it
through the interview.
You definitely can.
I hope you're right.
I just feel
really lucky today.
We have cake too.
What kind of cake?
It's got...
I remember you like
lychee, cherries, and mango.
Right?
(Nods)
He remembers everything.
He really does.
(Cake prepared by Zhao Xilun)
It must be nice.
Happy.
(Glances)
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
Are you the clingy type?
I used to be.
But I don't know if I am anymore.
I feel like I'm going through changes.
What does "clingy" mean to you?
I don't know either.
Do you think you need
a lot of personal space?
(Follows up)
(Tries not to laugh)
I guess it depends on
what you mean by "a lot".
I need some space to grow on my own
and some personal space when I need it.
But I don't need that much space.
Yeah.
Really? That's how you feel?
That's honestly how I feel.
So do you think...
Am I asking too many questions?
Ask away.
Do you think a sense of security
comes from yourself,
or does it come from your partner?
Sha Yue'er finally said
what's on her mind.
Your partner should give you some,
but you need to have it
within yourself first.
That makes sense.
What your partner gives you can help
keep that feeling alive.
But you have to have it
in you first.
Otherwise, no matter how much they give,
it won't be enough.
I agree.
Absolutely.
You're pretty insightful.
(Praise)
Do you know when my birthday is?
That question.
She's comparing them.
Do you know when my birthday is?
July 17th.
(Blurts it out)
You've got a pretty good memory.
Zhao Xilun really remembers everything.
What?
Nothing. It just suddenly came to mind.
Okay.
Zhao Xilun really gets points for this.
I am starting to see
your fearful attachment tendencies.
You know what fearful attachment is now?
I looked it up.
You tend to seek reassurance
about the same things.
Yes.
This doesn't feel like
an interrogation, does it?
(Watches)
(Puts down chopsticks)
Not exactly an interrogation,
but I can tell you are...
What?
Perhaps you are seeking
a sense of security.
(I can tell that you are seeking
a sense of security)
That is exactly right.
He can recognize
what she needs.
Yes.
I think I am somewhat
afraid to be vulnerable.
(I am afraid to be vulnerable)
Sha Yue'er is gradually opening up.
Are you afraid
when it comes to love?
Yes.
I look forward to it,
but I am afraid of it.
I want to get
closer, but I am afraid.
(I want to get closer, but I am afraid)
Perhaps I also worry
about what I can offer the other person.
Isn't that the wrong way to approach it?
Then how do you think
I should approach it?
You should start
with your own feelings.
Right?
(You should start
with your own feelings)
I feel like
I used to be very much like you.
For example, when I liked someone,
once she showed interest in me,
I would start overthinking.
I would start thinking
about how to make the relationship last.
What about the future?
The pressure would overwhelm me.
Now, I think I am pretty normal.
You don't think about that anymore?
I still do,
but I wouldn't let those
thoughts stop me from moving forward.
Because I feel that coming here...
To me, the house feels
a little like a utopia.
All the beautiful things
we have are here.
Yes.
Once we leave, we return to reality.
If you cannot be brave in the house,
how can you truly be yourself in life?
Oh, my goodness.
(If you cannot be brave in the house,)
(how can you truly be yourself in life?)
Zhao Xilun is genuinely sincere.
There is a reason
he earns her points.
Yes.
He knows how to reach her emotionally.
If you cannot see the stars,
don't be too disappointed.
It is all right.
There is quite a lot of light pollution.
It is difficult to see them.
"There is quite
a lot of light pollution."
Such a science-minded guy.
Let's eat.
You look even more like
a science guy with those glasses.
(Glasses)
Then I will...
put them aside.
I was complimenting you.
(Laughs)
I thought you meant
those thin black frames.
Like these.
Just regular glasses.
(After the second big date)
If you got those glasses,
I think they would look great on you.
I know the kind. The flatter ones.
No.
They have a black frame on top,
with the lenses underneath.
I have worn those before.
It looks more refined.
Yes.
You know what I mean?
I do.
Those look good.
(The day Zhao Xilun
goes to stargazing room)
(Pulls out the glasses)
Carefully selected.
This kind.
This?
(Puts them on)
Puts them on immediately.
I think they work too.
Actually, I think Zhao Xilun
is quite good too.
Look, you are...
(Shy)
Getting shy again.
Those glasses really were a good choice.
It really got to her.
I think I will just eat elegantly.
She says she will eat elegantly.
If I did not
care about you,
I would just
do whatever feels comfortable.
But because I care about you,
I feel like...
It is a very subtle difference.
There are so many little details,
from doing her makeup
to washing her hair.
Yes.
I think I will just eat elegantly.
Do you smell anything?
I sprayed the perfume you gave me.
(The perfume you gave me,
LunYue Full Moon)
I was going to mention it.
Yes.
There is something about this scent
that is...
captivating.
Oh, my goodness.
"Captivating".
I can't.
There is something about this scent
that is...
captivating.
(Captivating)
Captivating.
Very captivating.
Oh, my goodness.
Where do you come up with so many words?
He is so happy.
He cannot hide his smile.
(Cupid, Fiona Sit)
Sha Yue'er does have some
feelings for him,
too.
Yes.
If I had absolutely
no interest in you,
I would not look
at you the way I do, nor would I smile
like that.
So,
there is definitely
(Sha Yue'er has feelings for Zhao Xilun)
some fondness there.
It is just that the balance...
Is shifting.
There is some hope.
Yes.
I have faith in you two.
(Heart Signal Mini Scene)
He's not sure what to do anymore.
He is still processing it.
I think he is getting a little tired.
What are you doing?
I am drawing myself.
Draw yourself?
Yes.
Come on.
I really want to see you two.
(Very eager)
What do everyone's eyes look like?
I will draw it as a cartoon.
The head looks bigger than the face.
(Presses down)
Yu Yang.
(Tilts head)
(Stares)
The two of them are already...
Very close. Yes.
(Makes eye contact)
(Laughs)
I have noticed that you can
only draw round faces.
You...
That means I like round faces.
Success.
Now it is your turn.
My turn?
Should I draw the face first?
All right.
Round face.
Square face.
Square face?
(Repeats)
Square face.
Your face.
("Fang" face)
Square face.
Renfang.
"Renfang" face.
Everyone has a square face now.
That works.
You two...
(Yu Yang and Liang Renfang)
Well done.
This is very good.
It looks similar.
A finance guy's hairstyle.
A finance professional.
I have something for you.
So do I.
Oh, my goodness.
What are you going to do about that?
What do you mean?
Return yours
to them.
You return it.
I cannot return it.
Neither can I.
They bought the same thing.
(The night before)
Three, two, one.
Thank you.
It has a very Wong Kar-wai feel to it.
You took a great photo.
Thank you.
You are so good at comforting me.
This camera is actually...
pretty good.
Yes.
I want to buy one.
I am convinced. I am buying this camera.
I will buy one for you tomorrow.
I will buy one tomorrow.
I will buy it.
I will buy.
I already ordered one.
I already placed my order.
I ordered mine too.
Mine is already on the way.
Really.
(Exactly the same camera)
Even the batteries are the same.
Maybe we bought them at the same store.
Too in sync is not always good.
We are really on the same wavelength.
I mean...
A fashion statement.
Take it down the runway.
(Showing off)
Who else?
(Bursts out laughing)
A fashion statement.
Right here.
(Plays along)
Three, two, one.
This one looks amazing.
This one looks great.
Fang, every photo you take looks
like a once-in-a-lifetime shot.
Two.
Three.
So beautiful.
Absolutely stunning.
Let's take one together.
Come on.
(Leans closer)
(Leans against each other)
Perfect.
Such a pure and youthful look.
Absolutely beautiful.
They look so good.
Both of these are stunning.
It feels like two different people.
Twins.
- The older sister and the younger one.
- Twins.
This is Fang.
Fang.
This is Liang.
And this is...
This is Yang.
Yang.
Now we have
so many photos.
I am confiscating this one.
Then I am taking this one too.
I like it.
I like it too.
You have the same hairstyle
like yesterday.
(Laughs)
Wait, you don't?
How is it the same?
That question came out of nowhere.
You really know what to say.
You really do.
You heard that?
I heard it.
What did I say?
You said Si's hair
looked the same as yesterday.
But I am sure it is different.
Yes.
I only saw her from the side.
I only saw Cui Kaiyi once yesterday,
yet she noticed my hair was different.
You two spent
so much time
in the stargazing room yesterday.
He didn't notice the difference.
What is wrong?
Why did you go quiet?
No, I was just moving my chair.
Your hair today...
looks so different.
Oh my God.
Say it again.
Reset.
One more time.
Just smiles.
Si just smiles.
Where?
What's different?
Keep asking him.
I love this.
This part's different.
The front's different.
(Different bangs)
And?
(Smiles)
These two are watching the drama.
And
the little bun in the back is different.
How's it different?
Yesterday, the little bun was more...
There wasn't this little bun.
(Laughs out loud)
Yesterday mine was over here.
(Yesterday's hairstyle)
Really?
Over here?
Over here.
You even got the side wrong!
Cao Yiheng, do you still remember
Cui Kaiyi's hairstyle yesterday?
(Paying attention)
I remember.
(Without hesitation)
What was it?
It was tied up in the back.
It was like
(Yesterday's hairstyle)
a bunch of braids twisted together,
like a flower.
(Satisfied)
Easy win.
How many nods was that?
(Smiles)
My eyebrows hurt.
I feel like even if Cao Yiheng
didn't actually remember,
that answer
would still make Cui Kaiyi happy.
I didn't remember.
I was only looking at your face.
(Smooth talker)
You...
You Scorpios love doing stuff like this.
(Proud)
I...
I could even ask
about the day before yesterday.
Searching memory...
Brain working overtime.
(Smiles to himself)
It's in my notebook.
(A week ago)
I'll note down your hairstyle today.
You got it?
Even if I forget,
my notebook won't.
(Even if I forget, my notebook won't)
Oh my God.
(Cupid, Yang Chaoyue)
Isn't he a mural artist?
He could draw her every day.
A portrait every day.
(Six days ago)
(Five days ago)
(Four days ago)
He writes it down every day?
(Three days ago)
(Two days ago)
Oh my God.
(One day ago)
(I've quietly saved every version
of you in my heart)
Wait. Let me look.
Side braid.
Blue dress. Antenna hair.
Hair pinned up.
He wrote down everything about her look.
That's so sweet.
How long has it been
since you used a notebook
(Hairstyle diary, house edition)
to keep track of your partner's
hair and outfits?
People sure get diligent
when they're dating.
It's in my notebook.
That's so thoughtful.
But you wore a blue dress on Tuesday.
I honestly forgot
how I wore my hair Tuesday.
Cui...
Not bad.
I really don't remember.
(Glances)
Are you going somewhere?
(Asks)
(Responds)
Wanna take a walk?
Can we take a walk?
Sure.
Go.
It's fine. You guys go.
We'll clean up.
No, we'll do it.
You guys go take a break first.
(Rushing to help)
Go on. I'll clean up.
(Not backing down)
We're not leaving.
We'll wash the dishes.
You guys can handle
the rest of the trash.
(Teamwork)
We'll clean up.
Leave it there. I'll get it.
It's fine.
I'll wash them.
No.
I've already got the gloves on.
We don't need this.
Do you want it?
No, you have it.
Then I'll take out the trash.
Okay.
We're done. Need any help?
We're good.
We're almost done washing up.
You guys go ahead.
(Thanks for your hard work)
Thanks.
No problem.
Why don't I do it?
No, don't get your hands dirty.
I'll be faster.
What's that supposed to mean? I'm slow?
I think I get it.
You're just too thorough.
You wash them too clean.
Wanna play ball or take a walk?
Let's go outside and see.
Look, the stargazing room is still lit.
Yeah.
So...
no one pressed it today either.
How do you know no one did?
Then maybe I just don't know.
Wanna go down?
Let's go.
Come on.
Have you tried this?
No.
Wanna try?
Let's do it together.
Let me see.
(Shows him)
So, wanna try?
Wanna try?
Sure.
(Shy)
I guess we can.
I think so.
I'll catch you from below.
We need shoes for this, right?
Yeah, you need shoes.
(Helps her put on the shoes)
Too tight?
Just right.
I'll find you one in a sec.
There are gloves too.
(Liquid chalk)
I'll put some on my hand, then...
pass it to you.
No, open your hand.
Yeah, open it.
(Helps apply it)
Like this?
(Focused)
Slowly.
We have to jump down.
Yeah.
(Reaches out to catch her)
You're okay.
Let's go.
How's your balance?
Pretty good.
Pretty good?
(Supports her as she walks)
I'll show you first.
This is how you climb it.
Live tutorial.
(Reaches the top in seconds)
He's pretty fast.
You're telling me you've
never done this before?
No. I only started here.
And then you're at the top.
(Stunned)
Wait till I get down.
You made it look so easy.
Tired?
Pretty tired.
(Makes eye contact)
Which one do you wanna try?
This one.
That's the one you just did, right?
Yeah.
Push with your foot.
Just push off like that.
It's easier from spots like this.
(Guides her)
Let's do it together.
(Protective)
I'll stay below and catch you.
Just in case.
In case you slip.
I'm over here now.
It's pretty tiring, right?
Let me see how to move you over.
Yeah, move over now.
(Nowhere to put her foot)
Then move this foot onto the gray one.
(Holds her steady)
No, I'll get down.
Jump.
You can jump.
Go ahead.
Jump.
You can jump.
It's okay.
(Loses her balance)
Oh my God!
(Love this, keep it coming)
Why didn't they do this sooner?
It's soft.
Sorry.
It's okay.
(Awkward)
Sorry.
It's okay.
(Steadies her)
You get up first.
Wait, let me grab this.
Your shoe came off?
(Protecting her from a distance)
I'm getting shy now.
Look, you're blushing.
How can you not be shy
in a moment like this?
Those are everywhere.
(Reaches out to steady her)
(Holds her steady)
Get up.
Wait, my shoe came off.
(Smiles)
I look like a mess.
No, you're fine.
(Supports himself)
Now they're quiet.
(Rubs hands)
This is so awkward.
(Tugs at shirt)
(Looks down and smiles)
You look pretty tired too.
(Cracks up)
I am pretty tired.
That goofy smile.
Want some more chalk?
No.
We can climb together. You stay here.
I'll be over here.
If you can't get down,
just call me right away.
Love between two little geckos.
Recommend it to the others.
(Bohan, Xing, family of four)
Xing and Bohan.
Yeah.
They should come too.
Okay.
Anything else?
Nope.
I'm so full.
My dress can barely fit anymore.
(Helps take off the apron)
Okay.
Why do those two look
like an old married couple?
Just look at them.
Today, I...
(Smiles)
- What're you smiling about?
- Wasn't I the first one back?
And then?
Then I went straight over and dropped in
a Master Kong Jasmine Coin.
(Three hours ago)
(Heads straight to the wishing well)
(Wishing well, stargazing room, city date)
Going to the stargazing room?
Here we go.
(Cao Yiheng sends
a stargazing room invite)
Stargazing room.
(Cao Yiheng successfully unlocks
the stargazing room)
Did it go through?
Yeah.
I've noticed these past few days
the weather's been pretty much the same.
So...
I figured we don't have many days left.
So I went and used
a Master Kong Jasmine Coin.
So it's tomorrow?
Okay.
Are you free?
Of course.
(Are you free? Of course)
Absolutely.
Actually, we
could go more than once.
(Go more than once)
So you mean I should use
another one the next day?
Got it.
That's how it should work.
I actually wanted to use them all.
All of them?
Yeah.
(Yeah)
What's this?
It's a key.
There's a key too?
Invitation card.
Thanks.
Got it.
Invitation card.
Thanks.
(Hands it over)
Got it.
(Smiles)
These two...
It's so pretty.
(Stargazing room key)
A golden key.
Technically, since we have the key,
it seems like
we can go anytime.
What if we went right now?
That's too much.
You keep the key then.
You're writing letters again.
Is this part of your daily routine?
Yeah, every day.
Yeah, every night I come in here
for some time to myself.
A long-distance romance
in the Signal House.
Seriously.
You look so impressive.
So impressive.
No,
you two straight-A students
are actually saying I'm impressive.
You really do look impressive.
Oh my God.
You really fit this scene today.
You look super intellectual.
Really?
Writing here.
I will
grab the camera later
and take a couple pictures of you.
Okay.
Yeah.
Let's do that first.
Okay.
So cute.
Send it to the hospital.
That's genius.
But like this,
would Xing think
I'm trying too hard?
(Why's he so cute?)
So cute.
No way. Don't worry.
Trust me. Girls love this stuff.
(Girls love this stuff)
That's way too cheesy.
You could slip this photo
into the letter.
Just put it in the letter.
Then send it to the hospital.
Wow.
That's so touching.
(That's so touching)
Then I'll write on the back
that Meng took this.
Seriously, now I'm feeling it.
(Can't hold it in)
That's insanely cool.
This is kinda
like sending picture messages as a kid.
Take a photo, write a letter.
And Meng
keeps hyping him up.
Wait.
This feels so cheesy.
So cheesy!
A little cheesy.
Just write.
Go ahead and write.
Nice. He looks like a writer.
(Nailed the vibe)
Writing a book.
Me and Xing.
Xing and Me.
I'll send it to the hospital.
Keep writing.
We won't bother you.
Okay.
The One Chasing Xing.
Let's sit for a bit.
Okay.
Let me figure out this telescope.
What's she thinking?
Do you like stargazing?
Yeah.
I liked it as a kid.
I haven't done it in years.
(Glances)
(Squats down)
Let's find Venus.
(Glances)
Still nothing.
Why does it feel
like it's spinning around?
It's okay.
If you can't get it, come down and rest.
Sit for a bit.
I'm okay.
I'll try a little longer.
Okay.
(Squats down again)
(Glances)
(Tries hard to find the stars)
That's Venus and Jupiter.
Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter.
So Mars is between them.
I can't see Mars though.
Not with the naked eye?
When we have time, we could go
to an observatory.
Sure.
Let's sit for a bit.
Let's sit.
Zhao Xilun,
will we be able to see the stars?
Zhao Xilun.
Now that's a philosophical question.
That's not
an astronomy question anymore.
Why?
Because it's up to you.
It depends on how you look.
With your eyes or a telescope?
Or with something more advanced?
Okay.
So that's what you mean by "up to you".
Any books you'd recommend?
Biographies have stuck with me the most.
You like biographies?
Yeah.
Whose biography?
Uh...
Zeng Guofan's.
You know your history.
I really admire Qin Shi Huang.
I went to Handan
and visited his hometown.
Successfully met your idol.
I'm kinda jealous.
You really follow through.
(Cracks up)
You say it, then you do it.
(Plays along)
Yeah, and I went alone.
Even more impressive.
Definitely.
You're a planner too.
You're good at compliments.
You're killing me.
Every time I see you,
I can't stop laughing.
It's because I naturally radiate humor.
He always knows how to respond to her.
Yeah.
You've got such a handsome face,
but everything you say is so cheesy!
I'm kidding.
I know.
Calling me cheesy still hurts.
Protective younger boyfriend.
I actually like the protective type.
I can actually tell.
Tell what?
What you want
in a partner
is caring and protective,
not controlling.
Perfect reading comprehension.
Not the lecturing kind
who tries to control you.
Guys, take notes.
Do you think I'd prefer
someone older or younger?
I don't think age matters.
It's more about someone giving you
special attention and care.
Being thoughtful and considerate.
So you can just go
for whatever you want,
and leave the rest to your partner.
How'd you figure that out?
It's pretty obvious.
You can tell from lots of little things
in everyday life.
You really want
someone you can rely on.
That's why I say you're smart.
He nailed it.
That's actually pretty accurate.
One compliment and you're already...
getting carried away.
You hit the right spot.
I actually have one more thing...
You wanna ask.
Well, not really a question.
Go ahead.
I thought of a little activity.
We could make a time capsule.
Time capsule?
And after I write my letter,
you'll keep it for me.
Wow.
They'll keep each other's?
I didn't expect that.
I thought about it all night.
At first, I thought
about giving you flowers,
but you've gotten quite a few lately.
How do you know?
And I felt kind of torn
about it.
I thought if I gave you flowers,
you'd be happy for a moment,
then that's it.
And I'm not really sure
what really gets to you.
Since you like journaling,
I wanted this to mean more.
Wanna write one?
Sure.
Why does this sound kinda sad?
It's not sad.
I think saving
these happy feelings from right now
and reading them later
would be pretty amazing, don't you?
It would.
It's downstairs. I'll get it for you.
Okay.
That's so thoughtful.
(Sits up)
Sha Yue'er is happy now.
We can start with...
This is a written promise.
Oh my God!
(Letter of promise)
This feels so official.
Is this your handwriting?
Yeah.
This one's...
yours.
Maria!
Let's start writing.
What're you gonna write about?
I haven't really decided.
I think...
I'm kind of lost right now.
Writing it down might help.
Wow.
You picked the perfect thing.
Doing this while stargazing
really captures the moment.
Yeah.
(Glances)
Give it a title.
(Zhao Xilun starts writing)
That look.
Right now, I'm here with Sha Yue'er,
lying in the stargazing room.
From not daring to look at you at first
to taking that first brave step,
every step has been fun.
We're really alike.
I know you're someone who takes
relationships very seriously.
But no matter what happens,
I really cherish our time together now.
I think
if I make it to outer space one day,
I'll finally see the other side
of "Yue".
[*Yue: moon]
If I try just a little harder,
luck and opportunities
will come my way too.
(Sha Yue'er still hasn't
started writing)
(Starts writing)
Today is my second time
in the stargazing room.
We're sitting
on the second-floor balcony.
It's a summer night
when I'm 22.
Since coming here,
I've felt
emotional highs and lows I haven't felt
in a very long time.
Right now, I feel really lost.
When it comes to love,
I really don't know
whether I should follow my heart
or follow my head.
Sha Yue'er feels lost too.
I'm 22 this year.
I can still make mistakes in love.
But...
I don't want to be wrong.
We only have so much love to give.
It should go to the right person.
No matter how this ends,
this journey
has been incredibly precious.
I hope the choice I make
is fair to everyone and true to myself.
I'm done.
I'll wrap mine up.
I suddenly wanna
share something with you.
What is it?
Okay.
I'm a little sad.
(Sad)
What's wrong?
Our time in the house is almost over.
And sometimes it just feels
like time went by so fast.
We may never experience
anything like this again.
So we should cherish it.
That got deep.
I think this experience has had
a really positive effect on me.
It's made me braver too.
(Made me braver)
You weren't this brave before?
I really wasn't.
Yeah.
Because I knew we only had a month.
If I acted like I used to,
holding back and being overly cautious,
I'd regret it.
Wanna draw something on it?
Draw what?
I can draw something for you
without looking at what you wrote.
I'll just draw like this.
(Turns away)
I'll sign it too.
Who asked for your autograph?
No, you looked so sad.
I just wanted to...
Cheer me up.
He's cheering Sha Yue'er up.
I'll write "yue".
[*Yue: read]
"Yue".
Okay.
Wanna write something too?
Without looking at what I wrote,
can you do it?
What if I kinda wanna peek,
Chris?
Can you not look?
Okay.
This is kinda embarrassing.
Don't look!
I'm not looking.
Don't look.
(Blocks her view)
It's so ugly!
It's okay.
It's way better than mine.
Okay.
Do you think right now you're...
I'm what?
At your age,
does your head win out
or your heart?
In the house, my heart wins.
What about you?
I really don't know.
Maybe half and half.
Sometimes I can get...
really emotional.
I really overthink a lot.
I don't know how not to.
I think...
we just need to take our minds
outside of this house for a second.
This house really
is an amazing life experience.
We'll definitely
take something away from it.
It's because things
feel so good right now
that I get anxious.
Me too.
Life comes with choices and regrets.
They all help us grow.
Like going through a breakup or a fight,
or having a crush end.
It might feel awful at the time,
but everything we learn as we grow
leads us toward being happier.
That was comforting.
We'll always make
the choice that feels best
in the moment.
So no matter
how things end or what we choose,
we're still moving toward happiness.
(Every choice we make now
is leading us toward happiness)
That was really well said.
I kinda like
his brain.
So you really don't need
to overthink so much.
You just made something click for me.
So getting to meet everyone here,
and meeting you,
makes me really happy.
I'm really happy too.
Then that's enough.
So this is what being 22 is like?
(So this is what being 22 is like?)
But our 22 is pretty amazing,
isn't it?
(But our 22 is pretty amazing,
isn't it?)
It's amazing.
We can add our fingerprints now.
(Adds fingerprints)
(Letter of promise)
A Midsummer Night's Dream.
Will all of this end up
feeling like a fleeting dream?
No.
It's all etched in our hearts.
Sha Yue'er seems
like a nervous little girl
with so many hopes for the future,
but also so much uncertainty.
So a lot of the time,
she keeps
her fists tightly clenched.
When she's
with Zhao Xilun,
he'll gently
open her hand finger by finger,
until her palm relaxes.
He'll pat her hand first,
giving her this really gentle
sense of security.
Then he'll hook her pinky
and make a promise
with her.
Yeah.
I think
it has a lot to do
with her childhood experiences.
So she
needs someone
who can play that role.
Someone attentive.
Someone who gives her a steady
sense of support.
And gives her all
of their focused attention.
(Yue'er needs one-of-a-kind attention)
That kind of devotion.
He knows what Sha Yue'er needs.
Just now, Sha Yue'er wrote,
"follow my heart"
or "follow my mind".
She's unsure.
Could that represent
love at first sight
versus feelings that grow over time?
One grows slowly
as she sees his good side.
The other is more like,
at first glance,
I found you really attractive.
Yeah.
But I hope her heart matters more,
(Heart before reason)
and reason comes second.
Before, we thought
"following my heart"
meant...
Chen Hewen.
But actually,
Zhao Xilun is also
finding his own way
into her heart.
If I were there
as Sha Yue'er's friend,
I'd really wanna tell her,
actually,
you don't have to choose so soon.
I think
this house
is where things begin to bloom,
where the flower starts to grow.
(No rush to decide)
She doesn't have to choose.
She can take her time.
I think it's really cute.
That time capsule of theirs.
Zhao Xilun
has basically been writing
to her all along.
It's his way of opening up.
Sha Yue'er, though,
mostly used it
to sort out her own thoughts.
(Cupid, Sami)
This time capsule
almost feels like it
has a deeper meaning.
Maybe this isn't really
about heart versus reason.
Maybe it's about time.
His conversation with her
seems more
like he's giving her
another perspective.
He's saying,
how do you feel
right now?
What does this happiness feel like?
What is this joy?
Suddenly, it feels
like everyone else is here
looking for a partner,
while Sha Yue'er is here finding herself.
Yeah.
Psychologically speaking,
in this situation, Zhao Xilun
has always played
the role of a "third voice".
He understands her,
and gives her a sense of security.
He helps Sha Yue'er
move out of that anxious
state.
He lets her face
the uncertainty behind every choice.
That helps her
discover her real self
and
grow along the way.
(Don't go anywhere. The next episode
is even more romantic.)